// This is 'question.js' File of Fun2Learn 

// Question Array
let questions = [

    // Q: 01
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Where is Statue of Unity located?",
        answer: "Gujarat",
        options: [
            "Jharkhand",
            "Gujarat",
            "Maharashtra",
            "Goa"
        ]
    },
    
    // Q: 02
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Where is Gate Way of India located?",
        answer: "Maharashtra",
        options: [
            "Manipur",
            "Meghalaya",
            "Maharashtra",
            "Mizoram"
            ]
    },

    // Q: 03
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Where is Golden Temple located?",
        answer: "Punjab",
        options: [
            "Orrisa",
            "Punjab",
            "Nagaland",
            "Rajasthan"
            ]
    },

    // Q: 04
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Where is Hawa Mahal located?",
        answer: "Rajasthan",
        options: [
            "Meghalaya",
            "Maharashtra",
            "Orrisa",
            "Rajasthan"
            ]
    },

    // Q: 05
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Where is Kedarnath Temple located?",
        answer: "Uttarakhand",
        options: [
            "Sikkim",
            "Tamil Nadu",
            "Uttar Pradesh",
            "Uttarakhand"
            ]
    },

    // Q: 06
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Where is Taj Mahal located?",
        answer: "Uttar Pradesh",
        options: [
            "Jharkhand",
            "Gujarat",
            "Uttar Pradesh",
            "Uttarakhand"
            ]
    },

    // Q: 07
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Where is Charminar located?",
        answer: "Telangana",
        options: [
            "Telangana",
            "Punjab",
            "Nagaland",
            "Rajasthan"
            ]
    },

    // Q: 08
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Where is Rajiv Gandhi Statue located?",
        answer: "Andaman and Nicobar Islands",
        options: [
            "Chandigarh",
            "Tamil Nadu",
            "Andaman and Nicobar Islands",
            "Uttarakhand"
            ]
    },

    // Q: 09
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Where is India Gate located?",
        answer: "Delhi",
        options: [
            "Sikkim",
            "Delhi",
            "Ladakh",
            "Lakshadweep"
            ]
    },

    // Q: 10
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Where is Statue of Gandhi located?",
        answer: "Pondicherry",
        options: [
            "Orrisa",
            "Punjab",
            "Nagaland",
            "Pondicherry"
            ]
    },

];